Actually,
when we first met,
I already liked you a lot.
This isn't an im...
Actually,
from the moment we first met,
I've liked you.
This isn't an impulse.
I've thought about this carefully.
From now on,
I want to take care...
take care of you for the rest of my life.
From... From now on,
from now on, I want to always care for...
That was fast.
Hot... Hot Americano, no sugar.
Thanks.
Reviews say the movie we're seeing today
is really good.
We can go eat hot pot after the movie.
Sounds good.
The car should be here soon.
And then after we eat,
we can go for a walk or something.
I didn't really like the last sentence.
You... You don't want to take a walk?
We can do something else.
Not just you taking care of me.
We should take care of each other.
You heard all that?
You agreed?
Isn't this a bit too casual?
I... I bought a ring.
I custom-ordered one, but...
the shipping was delayed.
Never mind, never mind. It'll get here.
I was going to wait until it... it...
until it arrived to tell you.
I...
Say something else.
I'm sorry.
I will.
At the time, I thought
as long as I could be with him,
nothing else mattered.
You're back.
Is this your new draft?
But I'm not really happy with it.
I feel like I've seen
a similar storyline somewhere.
Maybe
good ideas are often similar.
I'm not sure if it...
You've got something right here.
What?
What is this?
Earlier this afternoon, I saw
a kid playing with it.
I thought it was hilarious,
so I bought it for you.
It's so cute.
You must be tired.
Take a break.
I'll go make something to eat.
You lived like this for two years.
I used to think
I could live like this forever.
He's trapped in that moment.
Which means
none of this will change.
It will never change.
He will always love me.
It's just an illusion.
I know.
But for a very long time,
I lost myself in it.
But earlier you said...
No.
No, no.
Of course not.
I'm not making excuses.
Understood.
I'll make the changes ASAP.
I'm really, really sorry.
I understand what you mean.
Today?
Tonight?
Sure, sure.
Deep breaths.
Deep... deep breaths.
Do you know how annoying that client is?
Everyone at my company is awful too.
They dump everything on me.
That proposal...
I can't possibly submit it tonight.
I even sprained my ankle on the way back.
I rode a bike back,
and the bike derailed.
I have the worst luck today.
You're hurt.
Want me to spray some medicine on it?
Leave me alone.
I'm sorry.
Today has really been
a terrible day for me.
It's okay.
You're cute even when you're angry.
Take a guess.
What's this?
When I passed by today,
I saw a kid playing with it.
I thought it was so funny.
A kitty.
Seen this way, it kind of looks like you.
Don't cry now.
No matter how bad my mood was,
having his sweet rice wine soup with egg
would instantly relax me.
Then when did you change your mind?
I was careless.
I naively thought
I had everything under control.
Careful.
I had a great time today.
Yeah, watch the steps.
I should really
hang out with you young folks
more often.
Yeah.
Careful.
Xiao Su, how old do you think Ma is?
He looks thirty.
Come on, what are you talking about?
He's not thirty.
He's forty-two.
Really? You look so young.
I really couldn't tell.
After you.
Careful, careful.
Wait a minute.
How are you getting back?
I called a cab, don't worry.
Why take a cab?
No, no, no.
Let me drop you off first.
It's fine, the car's already here.
Watch your head.
Get in.
We'll keep in touch on WeChat then.
Okay.
Destination set.
Why is it you?
Is this what you call networking?
You misunderstand.
Get out of the car first, hurry.
When did you become like this?
You don't understand. Get out first.
Right.
I'm the one who doesn't understand.
Fu Yan!
Help them, hurry!
Car crash! Everyone okay? People inside!
Call for help! Call for help!
Hurry, help them! Hurry!
It's horrific.
Call 120!
Hello, there's been a car crash here.